(Sheldon:)And that makes sense.
(Sheldon:)You'd think after Xbox,
there'd be Xbox 2.
But no, next came Xbox 360. Hm?
(Sheldon:)And now, after 360, comes Xbox One.
Why "One"?
(Sheldon:)Maybe that's how many seconds
of thought they put into naming it.
(Amy:)Can you get the butter, please?
(Sheldon:)You know, however,
with the Xbox One,
(Sheldon:)I can control
my entire entertainment system
(Sheldon:)using voice commands.
(Sheldon:)Up until now,
I've had to use Leonard.
(Amy:)Then get the other one.
Pass the butter.
(Sheldon:)Hang on.
(Sheldon:)I don't feel like you're taking
this dilemma seriously.
(Amy:)Fine, Sheldon.
(Amy:)You have my undivided attention.
(Sheldon:)Okay, now, the PS4 is
more angular and sleek-looking.
-(MOCKING) No way.
-Yeah.
(Sheldon:)It's true. But the larger size
of the Xbox One
(Sheldon:)may keep it from overheating.
(Amy:)You wouldn't want
your gaming system to overheat.
(Sheldon:)Well, you absolutely would not.
(Sheldon:)And furthermore, the Xbox One
now comes with a Kinect included.